Espy, Watt; Papers apap301
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1962-2007; Undated; 5; 7.5 cubic ft.; 7.5 cu. ft.
  - Hunt, Guy, Governor, Alabama, 1986; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Husband, Eliza, Louisiana State University, 1987-1988 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Illinois State Historical Library, 1977-1978 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Indiana State Library, 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Justice and Mercy Project, Steve and Lisa Haberman, 1987; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Kalish, Carol, Bureau of Justice Statistics, Department of Justice, 1983 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Kangwana, Juma, 1986; 1993 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Kelly, Jack, 1992-1993 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Keve, Paul, Virginia Commonwealth University, 1983-1987; 1989; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Kroll, Michael, 1988; 1990-1991 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - LaBranche, Linda, 1989-1990 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Likely Stories Inc., 1996-1997 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Lilly, Bob, Northern Kentucky University, 1992-1993; 1995; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Linebaugh, Peter, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Littlejohn, Nancy, Central Missouri State University, 1989; 1991-1995 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Los Angeles Times, Bob Berger, 1986 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Louisiana Coalition on Jails and Prisons, 1979; 1983-1984; 1986 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Mackey, Phillip, 1978-1980; 1982-1983 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Magee, Doug, 1980-1984; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Maguire, Andrew, Congress of the United States, House of Representatives, Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - March, Ray, 1978-1979; 1981-1982 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Marquardt, Ronald, University of Southern Mississippi, 1986 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Massey, Jim, University of Georgia, 1986 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Mastel, John, 1996-1997 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - McCluskey, Jim, 1996 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - McDade, Thomas, 1977-1984; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - McFarland and Company, Inc. Publishers, 1980-1981; 1984 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - McGivern, Gary and Friends of Gary McGivern, Marguerite Culp, 1983; 1985-1986; 1989 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - McMullen, Sean, Hunton and Williams, 1993 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Mele, Carlo, 1984; 1986 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Miami Herald, 1988 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Moore, Arch, Govenor, West Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1980; 1984-1985; 1989; 1995; Undated (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - National Association and Center for Outlaw and Lawman History, 1978-1980; 1982 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - National Coaliton to Abolish the Death Penalty, Robery Bryan, Bob Gross, Jedd Lubbers, 1983; 1988-1990; 2001 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - National Execution Alert Network, Decourcey Squire, 1984-1986 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - New York State Defenders Association, 1984-1988; 1990-1991 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - The New York Times, 1985; 1998 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Niemiec, Vera Bennett, 1987-1988 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Office of the Ohio Public Defender and the Ohio Public Defender Commission, Randall Dana and Anita Lunn, 1983-1986; 1988-1990 (Box 57 (5-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Office of the Ohio Public Defender and the Ohio Public Defender Commission, Randall Dana and Anita Lunn, 1991-1996; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Osmond, Humphry, 1982-1986 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Pacific News Service, 1988 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania State Library, 1977-1979; 1982 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Pepper, Claude, Congress of the United States, House of Representatives, 1986 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Perske, Robert, 1992; 1995; 1998 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Prejean, Sister Helen, 1985-1986; 1989; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Prisoners, general, 1977-1984 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Prisoners, general, 1985-1987 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Prisoners, general, 1988-1997 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Prisoners, general, 2000; 2002-2003; 2007; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Project Hope, 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - The Prometheus Foundation, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Radelet, Mike, 1984-1986 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Radelet, Mike, 1986-1988 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Radelet, Mike, 1989-1991; 1993; 1996-1997; 1999 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Radelet, Mike, 2001-2003; 2005 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Radelet, Mike, 2006; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Reddick, Bill, 1985 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Rouse, Albert, 1992-1993 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Schisgall, David, Fourth Floor Productions, 1991-1992 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Schrepper, Christian, 1988 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Schwarz, Philip, Virginia Commonwealth University, 1983; 1985-1986; 1988-1989 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Schwarzschild, Henry, 1976-1977 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Schwarzschild, Henry, 1977 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Schwarzschild, Henry, 1978-1986 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Schwarzschild, Henry, 1987-1991; 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Schwarzschild, Kathy, 1987 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Shelby, Richard, Congress of the United States, House of Representatives, 1986 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Shugg, Wallace, University of Maryland Baltimore County, 1987-1988 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Slovenko, Ralph, Wayne State University, 1988 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Snell, William, Lee College, 1975-1976; 1981-1982 (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Southern Coalition on Jails and Prisons, Joe Ingle, 1985-1988; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - The Southern Poverty Law Center, Morris Dees, John Carroll, Steve Ellman, 1977-1979; 1982-1983; 1986; 1999-2000; Undated (Box 58 (5-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Southern Prison Ministry, Jeff Blum and John Lozier, 1979-1982 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Sparkman, John, Congress of the United States, Senate, 1968 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - State Historical Society of Missouri, 1977-1979; 1983 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - State of Alabama, Board of Pardons and Parole, 1990; 1992 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - State of Missouri Department of Corrections and Human Resources, 1986 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - State of New Jersey, Department of the Public Advocate, Office of the Public Defender, Leigh Bienen, 1986-1987 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - State of New Jersey, Department of the Public Advocate, Office of the Public Defender, Leigh Bienen, 1988 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 7-8)
  - State of New Jersey, Office of the Public Defender, Neal Frank, 1988 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 9-10)
  - State of South Carolina, Office of the Attorney General, 1983 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Stevens, Leonard, 1988 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Streib, Victor, 1982-1987 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Streib, Victor, 1988-1992 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Streib, Victor, 1996-1998; 2000 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Streib, Victor, Undated (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 16-17)
  - Sturgill, Roy, 1981; 1983 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Sullivan, Robert A., 1982-1983 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Sullivan, Andrew, 1988; 1991 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Tabak, Ronald, 1994-1997 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Telephone inquiries and related correspondence, 1980-1983; Undated (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 22-23)
  - Tennessee State Library, 1977-1979; 1981-1982 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Texas State Library, 1977-1980 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Tolnay, Stewart, University at Albany, 1992-1993 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1984-1986 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1987-1988; 1990-1993 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1994-1995 (Box 59 (5-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1995-1996 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1996 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1996-1997 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1997 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Tomsovic, David, 1997-2000 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Tomsovic, David, Undated (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 6-7)
  - Toomey, Tim, 1988 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Vandiver, Margaret, 1988; 1991; 1997 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Van Raalte, Ronald, Law Enforcement Memorial Association, 1987-1988; 1992; 1997-1999; 2003; Undated (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Van Raalte, Ronald, Law Enforcement Memorial Association, Undated (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Virginia Coaltion on Jails and Prisons, Marie Deans, 1988 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Virginian-Pilot and the Ledger Star, 1986 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Wade, Dean Roy, The University at Alabama Law School, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Wallace, David, University of Nebraska, 1986 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Wallace, George, Governor of Alabama, 1966 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Washington State Library, 1976-1977 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Wasserman, Ira, Eastern Michigan Univerrsity, 1985-1986 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Weltner, Justice Charles, Supreme Court of Georgia, 1985; Undated (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - West Virginia University Main Library, 1978-1979 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - White, Exir, University of Alabama Library, 1977; Undated (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Wilkes, David, University of Georgia, 1994 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Williams, Gary, Circuit Court of Sussex County (VA), 1985-1986 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs, Leigh Bienen, 1991-1992 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs, Leigh Bienen, 1991-1992 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 25-26)
  - Woodstock Museum of Shenandoah County, 1982 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Wright, A.J., 1984-1985; 1988 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Wright, A.J., 1989-1990 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Yackle, Larry, 1978; 1983-1986; 1991 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence, 1961; 1964-1969; 1971 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 60 (5-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 2-4)
  - General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1981 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 9-11)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 14-15)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 16-18)
  - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 61 (5-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 4-6)
  - General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1993 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 62 (5-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1999 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, 2000 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, Undated (Box 63 (5-Correspondence), Folder 9)
- Biographical Materials, 1931-2008; Undated; 6; 2.56 cubic ft.
  This series contains materials about Watt Espy, including his speeches, published and unpublished writings, testimony, portraits, and news clips featuring Espy or quoting him. Of interest are files relating to his unpublished manuscript on juvenile executions and to a small signed portrait and autograph collection, mainly featuring members of the United States Congress. In addition, there are several personal items of Espy's: his typewriter, which he utilized well into the 1990s, his eyeglasses, his hat, and a special award from the National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty from 1991.
  - American Political Science Association panel, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 1)
  - Biography and vita, Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 2)
  - "Blackness of the Death Penalty in Alabama" pamphlet based upon studies by Dr. Bernard Bray and Watt Espy, 1985 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 3)
  - Crime and delinquency: articles and related correspondence, 1980 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Convention Delegate Certificate of Election, 1956 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 5)
  - Draft capital punishment history articles, 1985-1986 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 6)
  - Draft opinion editorials, 1985-1988 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 7)
  - Draft opinion editorials, Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 8)
  - Espy's hat, eyeglasses, and Espy Mercantile Company pen, Undated (Oversized 9)
  - Espy's typewriter, Undated (Box 65 (6-Biographical Materials), Item 1)
  - Executions in the United States, 1608-1987: The Espy File (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 9)
  - High school diploma, 1950 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 10)
  - Media tour for Alabama Prison Project, 1985 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 11)
  - Members pass, House of Representatives, 1952 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 12)
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Award, 1991 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 13)
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Award, 1991 (Artifact-box 2)
  - News clippings, 1977-1980; 1982-1983 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 14)
  - News clippings, 1984 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 15)
  - News clippings, 1985-1993 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 16)
  - News clippings, 1995-1997; 2001; 2006-2008; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 17)
  - Opinion editorials and letters to the editor, 1980; 1985-1986; 1991; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 18)
  - "Organizing Against the Death Penalty: A Handbook" with a brief history of capital punishment, Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 19)
  - Personal journal, 1991 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 20)
  - Personal journal with correspondence, 1966; 1968-1969 (Oversized 11)
  - Personal journal with correspondence, 1967-1968 (Oversized 11)
  - Personal journal with correspondence, 1974-1975; 1983; 1985 (Oversized 11)
  - Photographs of Watt Espy and his family, 1931-2001; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 21)
  - Planned juvenile execution book, correspondence and research, 1991 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 22-23)
  - Planned juvenile execution book, edited chapter and juvenile biographies, 1991 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 24)
  - Planned juvenile execution book, correspondence and research, 1992; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 25)
  - Planned juvenile execution book, introduction and sample chapter, 1992 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 26)
  - Planned juvenile execution book, new data, Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 27)
  - Reprint requests for Espy's paper: "Capital Punishment and Deterrence", 1981; 1983; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 28)
  - Signatures and stamp collecting ledger, Undated (Oversized 8)
  - Signed covers and autograph request correspondence, 1963; 1968-1969; 1971; 1973-1976; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 29)
  - Signed portraits, 1948-1985; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 30)
  - Signed portraits and correspondence, 1948; 1968; 1973; 1975-1976 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 31)
  - Speeches and testimony, 1979-1981; 1983-1984 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 32)
  - Speeches and testimony, 1985; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 33)
  - Statements to media, 1981; 1983; 1984; 1986; Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 34)
  - United States Navy service, Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 35)
  - University of Alabama identification card, Undated (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 36)
  - Washington deposition and related documents, 1993-1994 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 37)
  - Will, 1986 (Box 64 (6-Biographical Materials), Folder 38)
- Writings by Others, 1965-2002; Undated; 7; 2.5 cubic ft.; 2.5 cu. ft.
  Arranged alphabetically
  This series consists of published copy, reprints, and drafts of articles about criminal justice and capital punishment by other authors which Watt Espy collected. Authors include scholars Michael Radelet, Hugo Bedeau, and Victor Streib. The archivists kept articles written by others and sent as part of correspondence to Espy with the original letters in Series 5: Correspondence.
  - Agresti, David, 1983; 1985-1986 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 1)
  - Agresti, David, 1986; Undated (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 2)
  - Bae, Ronald, Dennis Wiechman and Jerry Kendall, 1990 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 3)
  - Bailey, William, 1974; 1983 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 4)
  - Barker, Kathleen A., 1986 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 5)
  - Barnes, Harry, Undated (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 6)
  - Beck, E. and Stewart Tolnay, 1990; 1992 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 7)
  - Bedau, Hugo, 1985; Undated (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 8)
  - Bedau, Hugo and Michael Radelet, 1984 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 9-11)
  - Bedau, Hugo and Michael Radelet, 1985 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 12)
  - Bedau, Hugo and Michael Radelet, 1987 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 13)
  - Bedau, Hugo and Michael Radelet, 1987-1988 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 14)
  - Bienen, Leigh, 1988 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 15)
  - Bonnie, Richard, 1990 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 16)
  - Bosco, Ronald, Undated (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 17)
  - Bright, Stephen, 1995; 1997 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 18)
  - Brown, Richard, 1979 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 19)
  - Cahalan, Margaret, 1986 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 20)
  - Catz, Richard, 1985 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 21)
  - Cheatwood, Derral, 1985 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 22)
  - Dicks, Shirley, Undated (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 23-24)
  - Dietz, Park, Bruce Harry and Robert Hazelwood, 1986 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 25)
  - Denno, Deborah, 1994; 1997 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 26)
  - Diaz, Sandra, 1985 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 27)
  - Dieter, Richard, 1992; 1993; 1996 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 28)
  - Disalle, Michael V., 1965 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 29)
  - Driggs, Ken, 1993 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 30)
  - Feldman, Marilyn, Katherine Mallouh and Dorothy Otnow Lewis, 1986 (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 31)
  - Frazier, Harriet, 1986-1987; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 66 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 32)
  - Frost, Brian, 1983 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 1)
  - Gale, Mary, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 2)
  - Gardner, Martin, 1978-1979 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 3)
  - Gautier, Bernard, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 4-5)
  - Geimer, William, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 6)
  - Gerstein, Richard, Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 7)
  - Jack, Gibbs, 1978 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 8)
  - Gillers, Stephen, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 9)
  - Gillespie, Kay and Barbara Lopez, 1986-1987 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 10)
  - Greenberg, Jack, 1982 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 11)
  - Griffith, Janice, 1998 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 12)
  - Gross, Samuel, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 13)
  - Haag, Ernest, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 14)
  - Harries, Keith, 1995 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 15)
  - Hart, Statia, 1996 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 16)
  - Helm, Ryan, Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 17)
  - Heline, Theodore, 1965 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 18)
  - Hughes, Thomas, Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 19)
  - Hubbard, Patrick, 1985 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 20)
  - Husband, Eliza, 1987 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 21)
  - Jones, Hardy and Nelson Potter, 1981 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 22)
  - Kaplan, John, 1984 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 23)
  - Kennedy, Randall, 1988 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 24)
  - Keyes, Denis, William Edwards and Robert Perske, 1997 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 25)
  - Kharif, Wali, 1987 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 26)
  - Krivosha, Norman, Robert Copple and Michael McDonough, 1982 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 27)
  - Koester, Pat, Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 28)
  - Kupfer, David and Norman Sartorius, 1988 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 29)
  - Lampe, Phillip, Undated (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 30)
  - Lassers, Willard, 1967 (Box 67 (7-Writings by Others), Folder 31)